capitalize on playing complimentary
football to go up 17 to three. Had a
nice long drive. You know, we got to be
better. We got to have better
communication collectively um in some of
those situations right there. But, um
lot that we can learn from, a lot that
we can grow from, and it's a lot easier
to be able to do that after a win. But,
I think there'll be some things that we
can definitely clean up offensively.
Obviously, you guys are going to ask me
about the field goal. I thought the
protection was good. We got to make the
kick. You know, we we ended up missing
the kick. Ended up hitting the second
one. Not very clean right there. The
snap felt like it was a little bit high.
Loved our punt operation at the end
right there versus um you know basically
a 10-man rush look that they presented.
We'll take the win. We'll look to be
able to improve and we got a great
challenge next week.
>> What happened?
>> I got an ankle.
>> I have no I don't I don't You think I
know all that stuff right now? Come on.
You're better than that.
>> The way the defense had the goal line
stand right there.
Momentum there.
>> I thought it was huge. You know, I
thought the momentum that those guys
established based on being able to make
that play um was huge to be able to go
into the half at 3-3 um just making them
snap it one more time and then I thought
offensively to be able to hit Devonte on
the first play of the second half and
then be able to find a way to go punch
that in then be able to get the turnover
and then that lead to a Higgby
touchdown. Felt like the game opened up
right there and it felt like we were in
control. You'd love to be able to finish
off some of those drives to close it
out. Could have taken the field goal to
go up 20 to three. um you know, could
have had some better spots that, you
know, we we'll keep growing. We'll keep
learning together.
>> He was awesome. You know, I I just found
out he broke the single game record for
tackles for uh tackles in one game for a
Rams. So, uh you felt like he was all
over the place. I I thought his presence
was outstanding today.
>> Similarly, what can you say about the
game play?
>> Big time, Nate. I thought he was
awesome. You know, it's cool to be able
to see him get his first two turnovers,
too. Um he's been around the ball. He's
made so many plays. He's so instrumental
in so many different things that we do
and he had a great game today. It was
awesome for Q.
>> What was going through your mind when
trainers are
off the field?
>> Well, whether it's Cam Cer, whether it's
Puka, you never want to see that. You
know, injuries are one of the worst
parts of this. Um, you know, he tried to
give it a go. Even Blake Corm came back,
ended up making some good runs in the
second half. I thought that was awesome.
You know, Puka tried to be able to give
it a go. Just didn't feel good enough.
And I apologize for that. I just don't
know enough about really what's going
on. and how he's going to feel and how
he's going to respond. He maybe could
have really pressed through, but we were
kind of more being smart than anything.
So, I do apologize for that, Sarah. Um,
but, uh, I don't like it anytime a
player gets injured, no matter who it
is.
>> You mentioned right to find a way. How
gratifying is it to have that kind of
win in a season where a couple of times
you were kicking yourself?
>> Oh, yeah. No. and and you know what,
because the defense played so well, you
know, fortunately that's not going to be
a scenario or a situation that we're
thinking about, but I think it's always
great to be able to feel like there's so
much improvement that can be had uh
particularly on the offensive side of
the ball uh for us to be able to move
forward. It's early in the season. You
don't take wins for granted. You know,
you certainly have learned that and uh
I'm really happy for the group to be
able to find a way.
>> Talked about coming out in the second
half without offense, that first throw
and so on. Do you something to them at
halftime or is it
>> Oh, yeah. I mean, you challenge guys. I
mean, and you try to be able to inspire
them to be able to play the way that
they're capable of and I thought there
was a lot of instances in the first half
where we didn't do that. Um, and it led
to some negative plays or turnovers or
turnover on downs. Um, even some things
that happened in the second half, but
you know, the guys just stayed the
course. I think the best thing that I
saw was the uh sense of urgency and then
the execution that occurred to be able
to allow us to go up 14 points and the
way that our defense was playing as long
as we didn't make a catastrophic mistake
felt like that was going to be enough to
control the game.
>> What were your initial thoughts on on
Troy and Shawn?
>> They did a great job. You know, I
thought uh you know Shawn did a nice job
finishing the game out when we kind of
gave Land Man a blow, but um I thought
we were excellent as a whole
defensively, especially after that first
drive. You know, they came out and you
know, the stats are going to show that
they were able to run it. The only time
that it felt like there was some leaky
yards was really on that first drive.
Even though we settled in and allowed
them to be able to, you know, just
settled for them kicking a field goal.
Um, can't say enough about that uh that
goal line stand that you guys asked
about earlier. I thought that was a big
momentum flip going into the second half
or going into the half and and then you
could feel that our guys took advantage
of that the way that the first six
minutes of the second half went.
>> That's awesome. Thanks, guys. Appreciate
it.
Absolutely. This is a team game. You
know, we're uh feeding off of each
other. I thought our defense did a hell
of a job obviously giving up three
points. That was a huge momentum um you
know, situation
uh down there. It was incredible effort
by our guys and execution. I thought
they played great really all day. Um,
you know, we did just enough to win the
game, which is the name of the game. So,
uh, we'll take it.
>> Yeah, just hope he's okay like everybody
else. Um, just hoping that he's, you
know, okay. I have no idea to be honest
with you what all of it uh, what, you
know, what's really going on. I know
he's as tough as they come and was able
to get back out there for some snaps.
So, um, we'll see. But just
um you know obviously a big part of our
team and a big part of our offense but
um I thought the other guys stepped up
and did a nice job.
>> How do you evaluate the offense as a
whole?
>> Um just a little hit or miss. You know I
think there were some times where it was
uh you know we were clicking and I
thought our guys up front played really
well. Um
um sometimes those days happen. Wasn't
uh wasn't the greatest of conditions. It
wasn't that bad but there you know it
was blown around a little But I think
probably more kicks and punts than
anything. I wouldn't want them been a
kick or punt returner today. Ball's
moving around a little bit. But um yeah,
I mean we can be better and um that's
the name of the game though. I mean it's
NFL football. You're not going to come
in every single week and go, I kicked
ass today and and I don't want to change
anything. So uh yeah, you know, there's
things that I would love to have back,
but we got a win and and we're moving
on. So I'm happy about that.
>> Knowing what they're missing offensively
and then it means to win this kind of
game where
I feel like we moved the ball up and
down the field last week and had 400 and
something yards offense and lost the
game and felt pretty shitty about it.
So, felt good about this one. Nice job
getting a win. I thought our off or our
defense did a hell of a job of, like I
said, getting turnovers which were huge.
Um, stopping them. Um, you know, still
got one of the best backs in the league
back there and our guys did a really
nice job of corraling them. Um, and you
know, we had some timely plays on
offense, scored some points, left some
out there as well. you know, got down
there um missed a field goal and then
and um you know, also had a fourth down
in there that um you know, really a
series down there. Had opportunity to
score um a couple times and didn't. So,
um clean those things up and like where
we're at.
>> How do you deal with
anything to those guys?
>> No. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, to be honest
with you, I felt like I could have put
them all in better places, too. You know
what I And I I sit there and I'm like,
man, there's going to be times where
they're open, I'm going to miss them.
There's going to be times where those
guys are open, I'm going to hit them and
they're going to drop it. It's it's
football and it's not perfect. We want
to be striving for it, but the last
thing we can do is, you know, get tight
about it and sit there and go, "Ah, you
know, I got to throw it even better or I
got to catch it even better." Man, just
go play. Trust yourself. Realize that
mistakes are going to happen. Um, I
trust every single one of those guys. I
could have thrown the ball better in
certain aspects today. There's no
question about it. But uh find a way to
win the game, man. That's that's what it
boils down to.
>> From the first play of that third
quarter where you hit Devonte Adams,
your offense looked significantly
different from that third quarter. What
clicked?
>> Uh I think just execution, you know what
I mean? Uh there were opportunities in
the first half I thought where we were
really pushing it, pushing it, pushed
the tempo and really had some shots and
just didn't hit them. Um and we hit
them, you know, we hit them uh in the
third quarter and and uh you know, put
up some points pretty quick. So, um,
just got to continue to work on our
execution, continue to, um, trust each
other, go out there and play and and,
uh, gain experience and and win games
along the way.
>> Probably ask the defense. Um, you know,
I thought it was a hell of a design by
Shawn. Um, to be honest with you, got
Higs loose in the flat. We, um, you
know, played quickly at the line of
scrimmage. Didn't give him a whole bunch
of time to sit there and talk and think
about it. Um it's great design and uh I
mean can't get more open than that. Just
try to throw it to him and let him do
his thing.
>> What did you see on the uh fourth down
play to Kir and just
>> how great was the catch that he was able
to make?
>> Oh, it was ridiculous. Um unbelievable.
Uh they they they had us covered up
pretty good. Um you know, tried to click
through and and couldn't find anybody. I
tried to buy some time to my left. I
don't know. Could I have run it? I have
no idea. There might have been 50 yards
in front of me. I just sometimes never
think about it. Um but uh you know saw
Kiran peeling back and and getting uh
getting loose and try to you know give
him a chance and he did an unbelievable
job fighting back for it. I thought
Dvonte did the same thing um on the deep
ball down the right side just fighting
back for the ball um you know on some
throws that Kyron's catch was
unbelievable but you know the one to
Devonte was a little bit a little bit
short.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh yeah I mean it's just I I love this
game. I love the history of it. Um I
remember being a little kid watching NFL
films growing up. Everybody's watching
cartoons. I was watching that. So, um
it's uh it means, you know, it means a
lot. I don't think about it on a daily
basis, but when it comes up, um I have a
ton of reverence and respect for this
game and the people that have come from,
you know, come before me and played it.
So, uh just to be mentioned with those
guys, uh is really humbling and and
something that, uh, you know, I'm sure
when I'm done playing I'll I'll think
about more. But, you know, kind of one
of those, you know, pinch yourself
moments where you're sitting there
going, "Man, remember watching him do
his thing and and uh just thinking he
was unbelievable." And being able to uh,
you know, be in the same breath is
pretty cool.
>> Thanks,
couple weeks ago. You talk about how
you're big on manifesting things.
manifesting the pick. So, did you you
think today would be the day to get the
first one?
>> Yeah, I felt like I was in a drought.
You know, year four, you know, I finally
get my first one. I've been in a lot of
opportunities to get one and haven't did
it. And to be able to do that today was
it was, you know, it was a great
feeling. Felt like a big weight off my
shoulders. Um, the biggest thing about
it is manifestation is a real thing. No
doubt about it. You know, you have to
speak it and put it into existence to be
able to, you know, accomplish the things
that you want to. And that was exactly
that. It was interesting because during
the week guys are like, "Man, you're
going to get one. You're going to get
one." And you kind of hear it and you're
like, "Okay, you know, I'm just going to
keep staying to my preparation, do what
I do during the week, but you know, for
it to actually come to life is you got
to believe in it, you know." So, um,
it's that was just all really truly
believing in the preparation during the
week.
>> What did you see on that?
>> We had, you know, what's funny is that
down in distance and that play came up
in practice many of times, you know, but
they ran it a little bit differently.
And you know, when we had it in
practice, it was Zay Flowers at the Z
and it was um DeAndre Hopkins at the F.
And Zay Flowers was always, we knew he
was the move guy, but they switched it
up. They had Isaiah Likely as the move
guy. He moved in. I told Emanuel, I was
like, "Hey, you know, you just stay
down. I stay on Z Flowers." Cuz you
know, a lot of that times you want to
get a free release. You know, the
receivers when you do a motion and stuff
like that, you want to get receivers a
free release. I was like, "I'm just
going to stay up there and press." And I
was, that's, you know, to your point was
just trusting the preparation and I had
gotten that same route. I was like, you
know what, I'm just going to undercut
it. If he throws a ball, I know it's
going to be a pick. And that's exactly
what happened.
>> Even with your preparation, like how
difficult is it to recognize that change
in real time based on the look you've
been preparing for most?
>> Yeah, it's tough. Um, you know,
sometimes
they we don't have a contract with them,
so they could do that and not run that
play, but you play the odds. You know, I
I talk about it all the time. There's a
calculated anticipation. You know, you
take that's one of the one of the things
I wanted to do this year was take
calculated risks and you know, you see
it and you go get it. And that's exactly
what that was
>> in this building in this town.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, it's huge. I think that fourth
down stop on the goal line was, you
know, one of the plays of the game. you
know, that's football is all about
momentum. And when you have a huge
momentum shift like that where, you
know, we keep they keep trying to get
in, keep trying to get in, and we keep
stopping them. Um, it's huge. And you
could just tell there was a there was a
big momentum shift. You know, it might
have not been loud obviously because we
got it, but you know, there was a
momentum shift, and then we kind of took
off from that point, but um, you know,
shout out to them. They kept trying it,
but, you know, at the end of the day, it
was about us locking in each and every
snap and giving it our all every every
time we got out there.
Baltimore. How do you take that prep?
>> It's not unfamiliar. And you got to
think about it. Last year when we had
the fires in LA, we kind of stayed in
Arizona. So, kind of similar thing
where,
>> you know, you're in an unfamiliar
environment. You are all, you know, it's
just the team and the staff. Um, but
they do a great job of getting us
prepared. We'll get our bodies back
right. Obviously, nothing truly is going
to change in terms of our uh routine,
but we're just going to be in a
different place. And honestly, I love it
because it's fun. It's fun for us. It's
fun to be in a different environment.
You can really just lock in on football
and focus on the task at hand.
>> I think we did all right. I mean, what
Lman had 17 tackles, so we weren't we
weren't, you know, the prime factor in
that. And I know a bunch of guys on
Dline had a lot of tackles. So they did
an absolutely fantastic job, you know,
stopping the run with a back that was,
you know, one of the top five backs in
the league. And that's kind of been the
consistent theme. You know, we had
Christian McCaffrey, we had, um,
Seaquan, you know, uh, we had Jonathan
Taylor, and they've been doing a
fantastic job of stopping these, you
know, really, really good, talented
backs, and this was just another
showcase of what they're capable of
doing, and they put it on display today.
>> Jared the ball. Yeah, it was a great
play. Um, you know, when you hustle to
the ball and you know, sometimes you get
lucky and that's what that is. Um, Jared
made a phenomenal play. Um, but you
know, for me it was just always hustling
to the ball. My dad talks about that all
the time is good things happen for to
those who run and that's was just a
prime example of that. So, um, you know,
guys were telling me I should have
scored. I got to check the film. They
were saying I was slow, this and that.
Like I made the wrong cut. I should have
been in the end zone. But, um, it's
going to be interesting. I got to look
back at it. Um, they were giving me a
little bit of crap for not scoring, but
you know, luckily the offense got in the
end zone, so it was all good.
>> Question was about
>> Hey, I already look, I already answered.
I said it was a phenomenal play, man.
>> Just real quick, you touched on
performance a little bit earlier. What
did you make of his day?
>> Yeah, he had a he was all over the
place. Um, you know, we talked about
guys and great additions and, you know,
he's really really showing of who he can
be in this league and He's done a
phenomenal job of stopping the run last
week. He did a great job of stopping the
pass, too. He's just allaround
linebacker, and he talked about it in
one of his interviews that I saw. He
wants to really bring that true Mike
linebacker back, and I think he's doing
a fantastic job of that.
Oh,
I feel like that kind of revived us. You
know, we kind of, you know, had a
mistake here and there, was able to let
them get in the red zone, get that close
to the goal line. But, you know,
everybody does their job. I was just in
the right space doing what I had to do.
Got one blocker, got the next one, and
he was right there. I just had to bring
him down to the ground. I think that
kind of shifted the whole momentum of
the game.
>> What did you see on your first? That was
a fumble, but you know, whatever. Hey,
they didn't call it. Nobody was catching
me. I was like 40 yards deep. Kind of
wasted energy. Could have just took a
knee, I guess, but whatever.
>> When you were a kid, did you look at a
lot more defenses,
what's it mean for you to get out of
here, not just?
>> Yeah, I mean, me and Dez Johnson were
talking about this on the way out like
when I was a kid, Ray. Louis was the
dude like you know you see the way he
hawks the ball the way like anybody that
comes across his face had to be
punished. I'm watching him I'm like damn
that's crazy and like you get you know
you get to step in the you know area
that he was able to dominate. I'm like
damn like this is kind of like surreal
just to know that like he was there. I
thought I saw some ball dude thought it
was him. But you know what
[Music]
to play this well in in that same house
that Ray Lewis built defensively. What's
that mean to you?
>> It means a lot. I mean, I know like, you
know, we're not obviously we're not the
Ravens with the Rams. But to be able to
like stack up the same, you know, kind
of defense that they able to have where
they're just like you have to be
punished no matter where you are,
whether you're on the one yard line or
whether you're on the minus 40, like you
not getting in the end zone. And, you
know, we were able to give them the
three points, but that was just because
of mistakes on our end. Wasn't filling
the gaps. I wasn't carrying on the back
side. The front wasn't, you know,
everybody was just wasn't doing their
job collectively. And then after that,
we just got right in our positions.
you guys a little bit early down.
>> Oh yeah. No, it changed everything. I
mean, we kind of realized in that run
game they're not really designed to get
to the edge and the way they'll take the
edge is if it's kind of like egregiously
open. So, we kind of tried to fix that
by, you know, heavy a little bit more
this way, doing a little bit more that,
adding a little bit more bigger
personnel just to stop the upfront kind
of uh problems that we were having. But
after that, it was just it was easy.
>> Talk a little bit operations, not
knowing who was going to play
quarterback, how you
talk about your preparation with all the
dangers.
>> I mean, yeah, we we were almost pretty
like confident that it wasn't going to
be Lamar. I feel like we was like almost
100% honest about it. But, you know,
knowing uh the different challenges that
both the quarterbacks that they do have
available kind of permit, you know, one
can throw the ball a little bit faster,
one has legs that can kind of get you
all around. And I'm saying that like the
other one didn't juke me out. So, that's
a problem in of its own concern. But,
you know, kind of you just get different
challenges with different quarterbacks.
Not every quarterback's the same. The
way uh you know, Stafford plays is
different than Lamar. The way Lamar
plays is different than this guy. Like
everyone's just so differently. So you
just got to be prepared for the
different challenges.
>> Quinton like we hear a lot about how he
does a lot of things that maybe just
don't jump out that you can't
necessarily see easily. How do you how
do you feel that as a pass?
>> Oh, you feel you know you get that one
little extra second because you know Q
kind of is just right in the zone where
the quarterback wants to throw it. He
can't do that. You know it helps us so
much with you know this is happening
that's happening. So much is happening
at different levels, but knowing that
they're able to lock it down on the back
end, you know, with Q, with, you know, L
man, with all these different, you know,
guys on the second, you know, middle,
second level, it it just helps you a
lot. I mean, you see how much we able to
get home on that last little stretch
because they was locking it up and it
was forced to throw.
Thanks.